popcash.net 2015-05-11

# Privacy Policy | PopCash.Net

**PopCash.Net** have a strong commitment to protect the privacy of its users. Our privacy policy aims to ensure the protection of privacy of our users and to provide them with control over the decision how their information is being used. 

### Acceptance of Terms

By using or visiting **PopCash.Net** , you agree to be bound by this Policy. If you do not agree with this Policy, please do not use our website or our services.

### Change of Policy

**PopCash.Net** reserves the right to change or modify the Policy at any time, without prior notice, by posting the modified Policy on the website. Your continued use of our service indicates your acceptance of any revised Policy.

### Information Gathered

**PopCash.Net** collects personal information only about its registered users (for purposes of providing the service and making necessary payments or payment collection) and collects non-personally identifiable information from its Publishers users and visitors to improve the performance of the website and service and to assure quality of the service and enrichment of the offerings to Publishers, Advertisers and their users and Visitors. In the process of registration or use of the service, you may be required to provide personal information including, but not limited to, User Name, Password, First and Last Name, Email Address, Country and other identifying information (including payment information).

**PopCash.Net** may further collect information about the time, type and manner of use of the Service. This information may include information regarding the IP Address, time of usages, and other information regarding the use of the website.

### Data and Information security

**PopCash.Net** is committed to protect the security of its users data and information and will take necessary steps to assure data and information security. Access to personally identifying information will be protected and controlled by password and restricted permissions. However, by using the website or service, you agree that **PopCash.Net** will not be liable for any third party action, misuse, abuse or infringement of data and information security.
